Finding Aid for Jeffrey R. Parsons papers, 1960-2013
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Maps 1960-1984
  The Maps Series, 1960-1984 (18 linear feet and 1 oversize folder) contents are arranged in three subseries, photo mosaics, tracings, and Peru maps. The materials in all subseries are arranged by archaeological site. The photo mosaics are 50 x 50 cms 1:5000 aerial photo prints that can be set up together into one mosaic of the sit e. The second subseries is made up of what was originally 9 tube boxes with rolled map tracings of the 1:5000 survey photo mosaics. These can be three to five feet wide and may include references to the corresponding site mosaic section. Some of the aerial photos used for the mosaics and prints were the product of an earlier flight and may have been used for different surveys in different years. Three Zumpango files that were received with the map tracings have been housed with the site materials. The third subseries holds maps of Peru, particularly of the Upper Mantaro Region. These have been housed in oversize folders.
  - Photo Mosaics
    - Texcoco, 1967-Texcoco Region 1967 Survey 1:5000 airphotos (Box 33)
    - Chalco 1969-1965 flight 1969 survey (Box 34)
    - 1965 Flight 1972 Survey (Box 35)
    - Chalco-Xochimilco 1972-1971 flight and 1972 survey (Box 36)
    - Zumpango airphotos 1973-1973 survey-traced (Box 37)
    - Zumpango airphotos 1973-1973 survey-traced (Box 38)
  - Rolled Tracings
    - Chalco I
      - Middle formative (also early Formative) Jeff Mary Xochimilco Milpa Alta (Box 39)
      - Ixtapalapa 1:25000 with sites (Box 39)
      - Chalco region-updated version (Box 39)
      - 1972 Survey Settlement Maps for INAH informe (Box 39)
      - 1972 Aztec Huexoculco Tlamanalco Ozumba (Box 39)
      - 1972 Classic Mary, Wenke, Prahl-Huexoculco Tlamanalco Ozumba (Box 39)
      - 1972 Classic Jeff-Tlalpan Topilejo (Box 39)
      - 1972 Late Formative Popocatepetl Ixtaccihuatl (Box 39)
      - Brown craft paper (Box 39)
      - 1972 Terminal Formative Mary, Wenke, Prahl-Huexoculco Tlamanalco Ozumba (Box 39)
      - 1972 Terminal Formative Jeff-Tlalpan Topilejo (Box 39)
      - SE Teo Valley Tlalmanalco (Box 39)
      - 1972 Early Toltec Huexoculco Tlamanalco Ozumba (Box 39)
      - 1972 Early Toltec Jeff-Tlalpan Topilejo (Box 39)
      - 1972 Early Toltec Mary, Prahl-Huexoculco Tlamanalco Ozumba (Box 39)
      - 1972 Late Formative Mary, Wenke, Prahl-Huexoculco Tlamanalco Ozumba (Box 39)
      - 1972 Late Formative Jeff-Tlalpan Topilejo (Box 39)
      - 1972 Late Formative Prahl-Ixtaccihuatl Popocatepetl (Box 39)
      - 1972 Late Toltec Original Ink Tracings-MW (Box 39)
      - 1972 Terminal Formative Tlalpan Topilejo (Box 39)
      - 1972 Early Toltec Xochimilco (Box 39)
    - Chalco II
      - Amecameca Basin Survey Map #2-Area B, Map 1-Prahl T-series (Box 40)
      - Milpa Alta Survey-D'Altroy (Box 40)
      - 1966 Teo Valley NE flank Cerro Gordo (Box 40)
      - 1972 Rapid Survey Amecameca Valley (Box 40)
    - Chalco III
      - Chalco 1969 Map 1 (Box 41)
      - Chalco 1969 Map 2 (Box 41)
      - Chalco 1969 Map 3 (Box 41)
      - Chalco 1969 Map 4 (Box 41)
      - Chalco 1969 Map 5 (Box 41)
      - Chalco 1969 Map 6 (Box 41)
      - Juchitepec Area Wenke-B (Box 41)
      - Prahl / Wenke B (Box 41)
      - 2A 2B 2C 2D Wenke 1972 (Box 41)
      - 2E 2F 3B 3D 3F Prahl Area Wenke 1972 (Box 41)
      - 4A 4B 4C 4D 4E 4F 9B 9D 9F 3A 3C 3E Prahl 1972 (Box 41)
      - 8B 8D 5A 5C 5B 5D Mary 1972 (Box 41)
      - 8F 5E 5F Mary 1972 (Box 41)
      - 7A 7C 12D 12F Mary 1972 (Box 41)
      - 1A 1B 1C 1D 6B 6D 6C 6A 5A 5B 7B 7D 8B Mary-Wenke 1972 (Box 41)
      - 13A 13B 13C 13D 14A 14B 14C 14D JRP 1972 (Box 41)
      - 13D JRP 1972 (Box 41)
      - 46A 46B 51A 51C JRP 1972 (Box 41)
      - 12A 12C 13C 32E 32F 32C 32D JRP 1972 (Box 41)
      - 18A 18B JRP 1972 Chalco area (NE corner) (Box 41)
      - 16A 16B 16C 16D 24A 24B 24C 24D 32G 32H Wenke 1972 (Box 41)
      - 21D 21E 21F JRP 1972 (Box 41)
      - 22A 22B 22C 22D 22E 22F Mary 1972 (Box 41)
      - 23A 23B 23E 23F Wenke 1972 (Box 41)
      - 40B 40D 40F JRP 1972 (Box 41)
      - 39A 40A 40C 40E JRP 1972 (Box 41)
      - 46A 46B 46C 47A 47B Wenke 1972 (Box 41)
      - 52A 52B 52C 52D 52F 51E 51F 51D 51B JRP 1972 (Box 41)
      - 53A 53B 53C 53D 53E 54A 54B Mary 1972 (Box 41)
      - 54D 31A 31B 32A 32B JRP 1972 (Box 41)
      - 55A 55B 55D Wenke 1972 (Box 41)
      - 56A 56B 56C 56D Mary 1972 (Box 41)
      - 57C 57E 57F Mary 1972 (Box 41)
      - 57A 57B 57C 57D 58F JRP 1972 (Box 41)
      - XA XB XD XC 12B Mary Jeff 1972 (Box 41)
      - Prahl 1972 2nd (Box 41)
    - Chalco IV
      - Chalco Region 1969 Survey Aztec Settlement (Box 42)
      - 1972 Late Formative-Tlalpan, Topilejo (Box 42)
      - 1972 Classic Chalco Mixquic Tuchitepec (Box 42)
      - 1972 Early Toltec Chalco Mixquic Tuchitepec (Lower Part of 2) (Box 42)
      - 1972 Early Toltec Chalco Mixquic Tuchitepec (Upper Part of 2) (Box 42)
      - 1972 Early Toltec Huexoculco Tlamanalco Ozumba (Lower Part of 2) (Box 42)
      - 1972 Middle Formative Chalco Mixquic Tuchitepec (Box 42)
      - Late Formative (Box 42)
      - Terminal Formative (Box 42)
      - 1972 Late Toltec Ixtaccihuatl Popocatepetl. (Box 42)
      - 1972 Aztec Chalco Mixquic Tuchitepec (Box 42)
      - 1972 Early Toltec Tlalpan Topilejo (Box 42)
      - Terminal Formative (Box 42)
      - Classic (Box 42)
      - 1972 Early Formative Ixtaccihuatl Popocatepetl Prahl (Box 42)
      - 1972 Late Toltec Tlalpan, Topilejo (Box 42)
      - Late Formative (Box 42)
      - 1972 Terminal Formative Original Ink Tracing (Box 42)
    - Blanton, Untitled & Valley of Mexico
      - Untitled [3 Tubes Blanton Ixtapalapa Tracings] (Box 43)
      - Untitled [Rolled Tracings and Aerial photo map] (Box 43)
      - SE Valley of Mexico Airphotos 1965 Ayotla, Tlalmanalco (Box 43)
    - Zumpango I
      - I-L8-59A 59B 59C 59D JRP 1973 (Box 44)
      - II-L8-26A 26B Mary 1973 (Box 44)
      - I-L11-58A 58B JRP 1973 (Box 44)
      - I-L12-8A 8C JRP 1973 (Box 44)
      - I-L12-6A 6B 6C 6D JRP Mary 1973 (Box 44)
      - I-L11-66B Mary 1973 (Box 44)
      - I-L12-10A 10B JRP 1973 Xaltocan (Box 44)
      - 103A 103B 103C JRP 1973 (Box 44)
      - 106B 106D 106F JRP 1973 (Box 44)
      - 108A 108B JRP 1973 (Box 44)
      - 109A 109B 109C JRP 1973 (Box 44)
      - II Extra Incomplete (Box 44)
    - Zumpango II
      - I-L8-62C 62A 62D I-L10-1A 1B 1C 1D 1E 1F MHP 1973 (Box 45)
      - I-L4-44B 44C 44D Jeff (Box 45)
      - I-L4-1A 1B 1C 1D Jeff 1973 (Box 45)
      - I-L11-64A 64B 64C 64D MHP (Box 45)
      - I-L14-7-A 7B 7C 7D Mary JRP 1973 (Box 45)
      - II-L2-1C 1D Jeff 1973 (Box 45)
      - II-L2-3A 3D 5B 5D 1A 1B MHP 1973 (Box 45)
      - II-L11-42A 42B 42C 42D Mary 1973 (Box 45)
      - II-L5-24 26 MHP 1973 (Box 45)
      - II-L9-4A 4B 4C 4D Mary 1973 (Box 45)
      - I-L2-61-A 61B 61C 61D JRP 1973 (Box 45)
      - II-L5-29A 29B 29C 29D MHP (Box 45)
      - 101C 101D 101E 101F 101A 101B Jeff 1973 (Box 45)
      - 102G 102H 102I JRP 1973 (Box 45)
      - 104A 104B 104C JRP 1973 (Box 45)
      - 105A 105B 105C 105D 105E 105F JRP 1973 (Box 45)
      - 107A 107B 107C 107D JRP 1973 (Box 45)
      - III-L13-3C 3D Mary 1973 (Box 45)
    - Teotihuacan
      - Teo Valley 1966 T-A-233 (Box 46)
      - Teo Valley 1966 T-A-234 235 236 237 238 (Box 46)
      - Teo Valley 1966 NE flanks Cerro Gordo (Box 46)
      - Teo Valley 1966 T-A-230 (Box 46)
      - Teo Valley 1966 T-A-239 240 241 (Box 46)
      - Teo Valley 1966 T-A-231 232 (Box 46)
      - Chalco 1969 Tracing Xerox Map 4 (Box 46)
      - Toeotihuacan Valley Aztec Survey 1963-1964 (Box 46)
      - Teotihuacan valley Survey 1960-1964 Santiago Tolman and environs (retraced map) (Box 46)
      - San Francisco Olalpa (Box 46)
      - Texcoco (Box 46)
      - Carta de Clima-Mexico & Veracruz (Box 46)
    - Texcoco Tracings
      - Texcoco Region 1967 Strip I map 2 recopied from original in 1984 by MHP (Box 47)
      - Texcoco Region 1967 Strip I (Box 47)
      - Texcoco Region 1967 Strip I (Box 47)
      - Texcoco Region 1967 Strip I map 1 recopied from original in 1984 by MHP (Box 47)
      - Strip I (Box 47)
      - Texcoco Region 1967 Strip I map 3 recopied from original in 1984 by MHP (Box 47)
      - Strip I (Box 47)
      - Northern Texcoco Region (Box 47)
      - Strip II NE Quadrant (Box 47)
      - Strip II NW Quadrant (Box 47)
      - Untitled [Occupation in surveyed areas] (Box 47)
      - Photo Mosaic (Box 47)
      - Photo Mosaic-Strip I, II (Box 47)
      - Texcoco Strip III A, B & C-Map B Chimalhuacan (Box 47)
      - Texcoco Strip III De, E & F Upper Piedmont Strip II (Box 47)
      - Texcoco Region Strip II (Box 47)
      - Texcoco Region Strip II A 1967 MTH (Box 47)
  - Peru Maps
    - Upper Mantaro Survey Maps
      - Pomacancha (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Acolla (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Sincos (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Parco (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Jauja (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Concepción (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Apata (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Yauli (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Huancolca (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Departamento de Junín (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Pasco (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Lima (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Junín/ Ricrán (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Ondores (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Huancayo (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Canta (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Matucana (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Ulcumayo (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - San Ramón (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Tarma (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Palcapacha (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Paccha (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Maco (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Palca (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Acobamba (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Palcamayo (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - La Cima (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - San Pedro de Cajas (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Atocsayco (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Malpaso (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Chuquisyunga (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Cachipampa (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
      - Tarma (Map-case 233, Folder 1)
  - Ciudad México (Map-case 233, Folder 1)